{
    "id": "df3aafd43420421d8df346d08323f661",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. a nice time on this holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "am having"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7cea430e367b42e4b8e2494a98d1a895"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is Japanese. She ……………. from Tokyo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "comes",
                "is coming"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff1a3a7e74a042718bc47fc878e6688c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. your stay here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Are you enjoying",
                "Do you enjoy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7651dcd192447b4ba6f2cb8f1778188"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. on my computer at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "am working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40977bb3120b44908925d4f5192127e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "This semester, I ……………….. chemistry and physics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "study",
                "am studying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50a32a54b87e45818636e67fdfc6a96b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. my parents next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3fb61eb3e19c4551b37d7bfeaf429b0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… to go now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "is wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "369324ecf7cf415ead0fe57678f1383a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why ………………….. me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't you understand",
                "aren't you understanding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13ba6d3ab23648f7934dbbc9c363e41c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking …………………. cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is causing",
                "causes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c28df8c33e314e60a1d3422a7831e008"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… a lot of films recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watch",
                "am watching"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2afe4674830e4f6d894d684b0b2115eb"
        }
    ]
}